https://fairmfg.com/privacy-terms/

Privacy & Terms | Fair Manufacturing
Skip to content
Contact Us605-653-3247
HomeProducts Bale Processors 7200-LM Bale Processors 7200-LMH Bale Processors 7810 Bale Processors 7830 Bale Processors 7830-TD Bale Processors Loader Mount Snowblowers 639D Loader Mount Snowblowers 842D Loader Mount Snowblowers 948D Loader Mount Snowblowers Sourcewell Contracts PTO Driven Snowblowers 848A PTO Driven Snowblowers 954A PTO Driven Snowblowers 1060A PTO Driven Snowblowers Snow Body Truck InsertsUsed EquipmentAboutEventsEmployment
Fair Manufacturing Inc. Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://fairmfg.com (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When you submit a contact form through the Site, we collect your basic information including your name, email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as "Contact Form Information".
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information, Order Information, and Contact Form Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).  We may also use it for advertising and retargeting to promote our website.
We use the Contact Form Information that we collect to communicate with you to help you with your requests, and answer questions you have.
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
MINORS
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 16.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by phone at 605-653-3247 or by mail using the details provided below:
2900 Alumax Rd, Yankton, SD 57078, United States
P: 605-653-3247
F: 605-653-3800
TESTED. TRIED. TRUSTED.
2900 Alumax Rd. Yankton, SD 57078 USA
HomeAbout UsProductsUsed EquipmentEventsContact UsEmployment
LOADER MOUNT SNOWBLOWERS 639D Loader Mount Snowblowers 842D Loader Mount Snowblowers 948D Loader Mount Snowblowers Sourcewell Contracts
PTO DRIVEN SNOWBLOWERS 848A PTO Driven Snowblowers 954A PTO Driven Snowblowers 1060A PTO Driven Snowblowers
SNOW BODY INSERTS Single Axle Tandem Axle
BALE PROCESSORS 7810 Bale Processors 7830 Bale Processors 7830-TD Bale Processors 7200-LM Bale Processors 7200-LMH Bale Processors
Fair Manufacturing, Inc., A premier equipment manufacturing company, proudly serving farmers, commercial business & government agencies worldwide.
© 2020 Fair Manufacturing. All Rights Reserved. | Privacy & Terms
Website by Bluestem Media LLC
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. OkPrivacy policy
